mywebook.com 2014-06-25

# mywebook help - Confidentiality Policy - Privacy Policy

Mywebook respects the privacy of its users. 

The Privacy Policy (“Confidentiality Policy”) refers to the practices that mywebook follows regarding the collection and use of information you submit to us or information we collect about you through our services. It also refers to the mood or imitating the availability of the content you add to the system. 

1. About us. 

The company Publico Ltd, is active in Greece with its main activities being the development of innovative software. Its headquarters are located in Athens, Cyprus 2, 15127, Greece.

2. About the services of mywebook.  

The services that mywebook provides, are offered to the internet users through the website http://www.mywebook.com 

In more detail, the services that are offered by the website refers to the exploration of the internet, fast navigation, content personalization navigation, as well as collecting, organizing and archiving information from the internet for a broad or personal use.      

Each user of mywebook can become a “member” (which means that he will register and create an account on mywebook or connect through the social networking companies he is a member in). 

3. Information gathered by mywebook. 

3.1 Registration information. 

Personal information that is required if the visitor wishes to register on   mywebook.com is his email, username, country of origin and language. 

      3.2 Account information.

By registering on mywebook, the member can enrich their personal information by adding other personal data to his profile such as gender, profile photo, etc.  

      3.3 Registration information through partners. 

If the registration of the user takes place through a service partner identification, mywebook will acquire some of your personal information held by the partner (such as name, profile picture, email, etc). The information that mywebook will obtained from the partner depends on the privacy settings of the user.  

       3.4 Post information you publish. 

When the user enters any information (including personal information) in posts, notes or comments, mywebook collects this information and may make it available to a subgroup or to all its members. This publication depends on the choice of the users’ privacy or the public character of his publications.  

3.5 When the user sends comments or reports directly to mywebook, this information is collected and classified for arrangement or response. Public date on registered mywebook members can be publicly displayed to other member/ visitors to mywebook. Mywebook is not responsibly for the consequences of choosing disclosure of such personal date to third parties. 

4. Technical information for collection data.  

When a user interacts with the services and the servers of mywebook, the system automatically records the data sent by the users’ browser. Log data may include information such as your IP address (Internet Protocol) of the users’ computer, mobile device identifier and geographic location of the IP address used to access the internet, type of browser, operating system, the time and date of access and the website the user visited before mywebook. 

5. How does mywebook use the personal information data?

Mywebook may use personal information to communicate to its members, to face potential copyright violations, to protect defamation issues, to protect the safety of its members, to protect the rights or property of third parties and improve its function and services it provides to the members of its community. Mywebook is bound to not sell, rent or publish the personal information of its members to third parties. Mywebook can supply personal information of its members, only if they have the express consent to it, or if requested waiver of confidentiality, legal use, for national security reasons or detection of serious offenses. 

Mywebook uses administrative and technical protection measures to maintain the security of personal data of its users. However, they cannot guarantee to its members, the security of information they transmit with their own responsibility. In any case, if the administrators of mywebook are informed or detect an attempted breach they will electronically notify the users to take the necessary protective measures.      

6. Changing or deleting information. 

Each member of mywebook may review, update or correct their personal information in the settings in their personal account. 

7. How do you use cookies from mywebook?

Cookies are very small text files that are stored on a users’ computer when visiting certain websites. They are used by developers of the internet for efficient browsing of users on their websites but also to perform certain functions. More information on cookies can be found at: http://www.allaboutcookies.org/ 

On mywebook we use cookies to improve our services to the users. The information we record concerns dates and statistical usage of mywebook, visits from internal system pages and history browsing information. 

Most internet browsing programs have as default the acceptance of cookies. Each user can disable the automatic acceptance of cookies on their computer according to the instructions provided on the browser. 

If something like this happens, you may experience reduced performance or limitation on certain functions on mywebook. 

8. Where is the information collected and stored? 

As we have mentioned, mywebook is based in Greece. Nevertheless, the personal information we collect may get transferred and stored on your servers or on third party servers acting on our behalf (such as hosting service providers) in the USA and in the European Union. To make use of its services, mywebook must accept this as our policy. 

9. How long will the information me maintained for? 

Mywebook is committed to maintain the data of their members longer than is reasonably necessary in accordance to the purposes for which it was collected. Time determination may only be applied in cases of special legal or regulatory requirements for retention of information.   

10. How safe is the information?

You should know that, whilst taking all of the necessary measures for the maintenance and security of your personal information, we are not able to completely eliminate every risk of potential violations. 

11. What is the policy for children?

Children under 13 are not allowed to use our services or create a personal account on mywebook. If a parent or guardian is aware that his or her child has registered personal information without consent, you should contact us through the feedback service. In the incident that mywebook is aware that a child under 13 has provided personal information, they will be immediately deleted from our records. 

12. What applies for the third party websites that connect via mywebook?

The presence of links and references to other websites, services or third party apllications, there is a service for our members and that doesn’t mean approval of their contents from mywebook. Links to other websites may create users / members of the site and for this choice mywebook cannot be made responsible. This privacy policy does not govern your visit to third party sites and your access is solely your responsibility. 

13. Transfer of asset information from mywebook.

In case of transfer asset information from mywebook to another company, the company owner Publico may transfer your information to the new owner on the condition of the commitment of the rights and obligations as described in this privacy policy.   

14. Changes to the confidentiality policy.

Mywebook reserves the right to change or amend the privacy policy. Every change or update of the confidentiality policy will be published in this article. If some significant changes are made to our confidentiality policy, you will be immediately informed by a direct notice that will be displayed on the mywebook.com website. If you’re a member of the mywebook community, you will receive a notification by email that will ask you to review and accept these changes. 

Effective date:  01st October 2013
